pacsafe.com 2017-09-12

# Privacy Policy | Pacsafe

### Last Updated: 5/15/2014

Outpac Designs, Inc. (“Pacsafe”) recognizes the importance of privacy. Pacsafe will manage your personal information collected through the websites located at www.pacsafe.com and affiliated websites owned by Pacsafe and its affiliated companies (collectively the “Website”) based on our belief of respect for the individual and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. BY USING THE WEBSITE IN ANY WAY, INCLUDING NAMELY BROWSING, PURCHASING PRODUCTS AND USING ANY OF THE SERVICES PROVIDED THROUGH THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE PACSAFE PRIVACY POLICY (“Privacy Policy”). If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not provide personal information and please do not use the Website. 

### 1\. Information We Collect

We collect personal information about you to deliver the products and services you request, to help improve your shopping experience, and to communicate with you about products, services, promotions, contests and sweepstakes. We try to limit the collected information to support the intended purpose of collection. 

#### 1.1 Personal Information

We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways when you interact with Pacsafe through the Website. Some examples are when you: Create an account on the Website; Make an online purchase from us; Request customer service or contact us; Submit a review or post any User Content (as defined in the Terms of Use) on the Website; or Otherwise submit personal information to Pacsafe. Personal information is information that identifies you or is reasonably linked to you. The personal information we collect may include contact and payment information such as your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information. When you ask us to ship a product, we may collect information you provide us such as the name, address, and phone number of the recipient(s). We may also collect personal information about you through social media websites and services and from other sources. 

#### 1.2 Usage Information

We receive and store certain types of information about your use of the Website when you use the Website. Our purpose is to allow the Website to work correctly, to evaluate use of the Website, for marketing purposes and to personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience. Some examples include: We may collect technical information such as your IP address, the address of a referring website, the type of web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider and the path you take through the Website; When you purchase or return a product, we collect information about the transaction, such as product details and the date of the purchase/return. 

### 2\. Cookies

We use cookies to enhance and simplify your visit; namely, in order to offer easier surfing on the Website, to make log in easier, for internal security purposes, system administration to tailor advertisements to your preferences and the like. Cookies are small data files stored on the hard disk of the users’ computer. In addition to cookies which send information to us, we also use cookies which collect information and send it to third parties. An example of this is Google Analytics. Some of our cookies may collect and store your personal information, such as your name or email address. By using this Website, you agree to the placement of cookies on your computer and to Pacsafe’s access to cookies in accordance with the terms herein. If you do not wish to accept cookies from the Website please either disable cookies or refrain from using the Website. We may also use web beacons. Web beacons allow us to understand if a certain page of the Website was visited or if an email was opened or if advertising banners on other websites were effective. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject cookies, but note that doing so does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies used in conjunction with our Website. For more information about disabling flash cookies, see www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Website and you may not be able to access or use some or all areas and functionalities of the Website. 

### 3\. How We Use Your Information

Pacsafe uses your personal information and usage information to offer and provide our products and services and to support our core business functions. These include order or service fulfillment, customer service, internal business processes, marketing, including contests and sweepstakes, authentication, loss and fraud prevention, public safety and legal functions. Some examples include: To fulfill your requests for products and services and communicate with you about said requests; To register your account on the Website; To administer surveys, contests, sweepstakes and promotions; To provide customer service; To help us improve and customize the Website; To send you information about our products, services, promotions, contests and sweepstakes; and To protect the security or integrity of the Website and our business. To accomplish these purposes, we may combine personal and usage information we collect. We may transfer or disclose your personal and usage information, for these purposes, within our Pacsafe group of companies including, but not limited to, Pacsafe and any parent, subsidiary and associate company of Pacsafe (“Pacsafe Group”). 

### 4\. Advertising and Analytics Services

We engage third parties to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services about the performance of those advertisements. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of our Website and other websites, such as your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. The information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Website and other websites and better understand your online activity. We may also work with third parties to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign on other websites or platforms. In addition, many web browsers support Do Not Track technology. Our systems do not respond to Do Not Track signals. Nonetheless, if you enable Do Not Track and it is recognized by our systems, Pacsafe will not use information about your web viewing activities to tailor your online experience on the Website. Note, however, that our third party advertising providers may continue to use information about your web viewing activities to tailor advertising to your interests across different websites even when you have Do Not Track enabled in your browser. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and www.aboutads.info/choices. 

### 5\. How We Disclose Your Information Outside Pacsafe

Pacsafe does not sell or rent your personal information to any third parties whatsoever. We only disclose your personal information with your prior consent or as provided in this Privacy Policy. We may disclose to third parties, certain non-personal usage information regarding the Website. However, in such cases, your usage information is aggregated with the usage data of others and does not identify you individually. 

#### 5.1 Service Providers

We may disclose or otherwise make available personal information about you to service providers that help with our business operations. Examples are shipping companies, payment companies, credit card processors, financial institution partners, hosting and maintenance providers, data storage and management providers, marketing and promotional providers, and generally, companies that help us improve our product and service offerings and our websites. 

#### 5.2 Legal Requirements and Protection of Our Company and Others

We may disclose your information in other special circumstances. These include situations when the sharing is necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Pacsafe Group, our customers, our associates, or any other person, or where otherwise required by law. Examples include protecting the health or safety of customers, or addressing crimes committed on the Website. Pacsafe may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant, subpoena or other legally valid inquiry or order, or as otherwise required by applicable law. 

#### 5.3 Business Transfers

We may transfer any information we have about you in connection with a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of Pacsafe Group or as part of a corporate reorganization or other change in corporate control. 

### 6\. Your Choices

We want to communicate with you in the ways that you want to hear from us. If you no longer want to receive marketing messages from us, you can either change your marketing preferences by changing Your Account preferences or, by clicking on the appropriate link at the bottom of our marketing emails. Please allow sufficient time for your preferences to be processed. 

### 7\. How to Access and Update Your Information

Pacsafe takes reasonable steps to keep your personal information accurate and complete. You can access or update your personal information, including contact or account information, either by accessing Your Account or by accessing your newsletter preferences from the link found at the bottom of all newsletters 

### 8\. How We Secure Your Information

Securing your information is important to Pacsafe. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Website, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Website, and you do so at your own risk. 

### 9\. Online Protections

Your account information is protected by the password you use to access your online account. Please keep this password confidential. 

### 10\. Privacy of Children Online

We are committed to protecting children's online privacy. In order to protect the privacy of children, Pacsafe does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. 

### 11\. Links To Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites. A link to a third party's website does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over third-party websites. You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to the website. 

### 12\. International

As a global company, Pacsafe may process, store and transfer Personal information in the United States or in any other country in which any company of the Pacsafe Group is incorporated. Pacsafe requires that all companies of Pacsafe Group protect your personal information, regardless of where it is stored, in accordance with applicable laws. 

### 13\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Pacsafe may change the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. Please check our Privacy Policy periodically for changes. We will post the date the Privacy Policy was last updated at the top of the Privacy Policy. The changes will go into effect on the “Last Updated” date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Website, you consent to the revised Privacy Policy. 

### 14\. Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [Contact Us](https://www.pacsafe.com/default/contact-us).
